<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Chess</string>
    <string name="title_activity_menu">Chess</string>
    <string name="start">Click to start</string>

    <!-- Chess front -->
    <string name="horse">馬</string>
    <string name="car">車</string>
    <string name="minister_black">象</string>
    <string name="minister_red">相</string>
    <string name="scholar_black">士</string>
    <string name="scholar_red">仕</string>
    <string name="general_black">将</string>
    <string name="general_red">帅</string>
    <string name="gun">炮</string>
    <string name="soldier_black">卒</string>
    <string name="soldier_red">兵</string>
    <string name="river_name_red">楚河</string>
    <string name="river_name_black">漢界</string>
    <string name="black_side_info">Black Side Turn</string>
    <string name="red_side_info">Red Side Turn</string>

    <!-- select game -->
    <string name="chinese_chess">Chinese Chess</string>
    <string name="play">Play</string>
    <string name="tutorial">Tutorial</string>
    <!--Tutorial-->
    <string name="chinese_chess_basic">The horizontal line of the chess board forms 9*10=90 intersections, and these 90 intersections are the places where the drop can be made.\n
1, red first black after, take turns playing chess.\n
2. The game ends when one side "checkmate" the other (that is, when the other side cannot avoid being eaten).\n
3. The two sides can also negotiate peace.</string>
    <string name="piece_movement">
将/帅（King）\n
Moves one square at a time, forward, backward, or sideways, but cannot leave the "palace."\n
仕/士（Guard）\n
Moves one square diagonally within the "nine-palace" area.\n
相/象（Elephant）\n
Moves two squares diagonally, but cannot cross the "Chu River" or "Han Border," forming a "field" shape.\n
Blocking the "Elephant's Eye": The center of the "field" has another piece, preventing the Elephant from moving.\n
马（Horse）\n
Moves in an "L" shape: two squares in one direction (horizontal or vertical) and one square perpendicular to that direction.\n
Blocking the "Horse's Leg": If there is a piece adjacent to the two squares moved forward, the Horse cannot move.\n
車（Chariot）\n
Moves any number of squares horizontally or vertically to an empty space or captures an enemy piece.\n
炮（Cannon）\n
Moves like a Chariot when not capturing, but when capturing, it must jump over exactly one piece (can be either friendly or enemy).\n
兵/卒（Pawn）\n
Before crossing the "river," moves one square forward only. After crossing the "river," can move one square forward or one square horizontally, but cannot move backward.</string>
</resources>